Scenic Hudson Collection: Records Relating to the Storm King Case, 1963-1981
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 15. Series title, 1964-1974; 15; About 10 linear feet Boxes: 125 - 156 Folders: 1737 - 2067
  - Gas Turbines (Folder 1815, Box 131)
  - Gas Turbines (Folder 1816, Box 132)
  - “Utility Applications of Gas Turbines” (Folder 1817, Box 132)
  - The American Society of Mechanical Engineers Publications on Gas Turbines; 1966-1971 (Folder 1818, Box 132)
  - Gas Turbines - Scenic Hudson Material (Folder 1819, Box 132)
  - Gas Turbine Tabulation (Folder 1820, Box 132)
  - “Gateway to Hudson Highlands” (Folder 1821, Box 132)
  - Geological Data - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1822, Box 132)
  - Hempstead Wetlands (Folder 1823, Box 133)
  - Highways (Folder 1824, Box 133)
  - Hudson - Fulton Celebration; 1909 (Folder 1825, Box 133)
  - Hudson Heritage Orig. (Folder 1826, Box 133)
  - Hudson River Article - Jan. 1970 - Environmental Science and Technology (Folder 1827, Box 133)
  - Hudson River Compact (Ottinger Bill) (Folder 1828, Box 133)
  - Hudson River Conservation Society (Folder 1829, Box 133)
  - “Hudson River Estuary” Geographical Review; April 1966 (Folder 1830, Box 133)
  - Hudson River - History&Historic Sites (Folder 1831, Box 133)
  - Hudson River - Marine Resources (Folder 1832, Box 133)
  - Hudson River - Statements on (Folder 1833, Box 133)
  - Hudson River Expressway: Clippings; 1965-68 (Folder 1834, Box 133)
  - Hudson River Expressway: Clippings, 1969-1970 (Folder 1835, Box 134)
  - Hudson River Expressway: Hearings (Folder 1836, Box 134)
  - Hudson River Expressway: Proposal (Folder 1837, Box 134)
  - Hudson River Expressway: Objections Raised (Folder 1838, Box 134)
  - Hudson River: Pollution (Folder 1839, Box 134)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Clippings, 1965-66 (Folder 1840, Box 134)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Clippings, 1967-68 (Folder 1841, Box 134)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Clippings, 1969-72 (Folder 1842, Box 135)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Clippings, Undated (Folder 1843, Box 135)
  - H.R.V.C. - Con Ed - O.&R. Power Lines (Folder 1844, Box 135)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Misc. (Folder 1845, Box 135)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Reports (Folder 1846, Box 135)
  - Hudson Valley Contracts (Folder 1847, Box 135)
  - Hudson Valley - Geology (Folder 1848, Box 135)
  - Hudson Valley - Historical Materials (Folder 1849, Box 135)
  - Henry Hudson - Historical - Henry Hudson’s Journal (Folder 1850, Box 135)
  - Hudson Valley - Historical - The Sloops of the Hudson (Folder 1851, Box 135)
  - Hudson Valley Originals (Folder 1852, Box 136)
  - Hudson Valley Originals (Folder 1853, Box 136)
  - Hudson Valley - Pollution (Air&Water) (Folder 1854, Box 136)
  - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1855, Box 136)
  - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1856, Box 136)
  - Vandivert, Rod - Chronology - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1857, Box 136)
  - Conservation Research -Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1858, Box 136)
  - Development&Resources Corporation - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1859, Box 137)
  - Hudson Valley Project - “Rhine or Ruin: Herald Tribune (Folder 1860, Box 137)
  - Hudson Valley - Statements before Subcommittee on National Parks and Recreation; July 29, 1966 (Folder 1861, Box 137)
  - Updated List of Hudson Valley Files (Folder 1862, Box 137)
  - Indian Point - Scenic Hudson Materials (Folder 1863, Box 137)
  - Indian Point - Reference Material (Folder 1864, Box 137)
  - Indian Point - Clippings (Folder 1865, Box 137)
  - Interconnections (Folder 1866, Box 138)
  - Interested Individuals (Hudson Valley Project) (Folder 1867, Box 138)
  - Interior, Dept. of - General Statements of Purpose and Literature (Folder 1868, Box 138)
  - Interior, Dept. of - Storm King Mountain Proposal, 1963-65 (Folder 1869, Box 138)
  - Interior, Dept. of - Storm King Mountain Proposal, 1966 (Folder 1870, Box 138)
  - Interior, Dept. of - Storm King Mountain Proposal, 1967-71 (Folder 1871, Box 138)
  - Interior, Dept. of - Stewart L. Udall, Motion and Brief, 1965 (Folder 1872, Box 138)
  - Interior, Dept. of - Clippings, 1964-72 (Folder 1873, Box 138)
  - Interior, Dept. of - Advisory Council on Historic Preservation (Folder 1874, Box 138)
  - Interstate Planning (Folder 1875, Box 138)
  - Joint Legislative Committee of Natural Resources - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1876, Box 139)
  - Kitimat Tunnel (Folder 1877, Box 139)
  - Labor - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1878, Box 139)
  - Land&Water Conservation Fund Bill of 1965 (Folder 1879, Box 139)
  - Little Stony Point Gypsum Plant (Folder 1880, Box 139)
  - Long Island Sound Dam (Folder 1881, Box 139)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 1882, Box 139)
  - Moodna Creek - Proximity to Catskill Aqueduct (Folder 1883, Box 139)
  - Movie - Charles Eggert Productions - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1884, Box 139)
  - Mumford, Lewis - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1885, Box 139)
  - Nassau/Suffolk (Folder 1886, Box 139)
  - National Power Survey Advisory Committee - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1887, Box 139)
  - Natural Area Council, 1966 (Richard Pough) (Folder 1888, Box 139)
  - Natural Area Council, 1967 (Richard Pough) (Folder 1889, Box 139)
  - Natural Area Council 1968 (Richard Pough) (Folder 1890, Box 140)
  - Natural Area Council 1969 (Richard Pough) (Folder 1891, Box 140)
  - The Nature Conservancy - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1892, Box 140)
  - New Jersey Utilities - Yard Creek (Folder 1893, Box 140)
  - New York Republican State Committee (Folder 1894, Box 140)
  - Department of Water Supply, Gas&Electricity, NYC (D’Angelo) (Folder 1895, Box 140)
  - New York State Council of Parks (Land Use Study) (Folder 1896, Box 140)
  - Newspaper Guild of NY (Folder 1897, Box 140)
  - Noise Pollution (Folder 1898, Box 140)
  - Nuclear Plants L.I. Lighting Company (Folder 1899, Box 140)
  - Nuclear Power, 1965-68 (Folder 1900, Box 140)
  - Nuclear Power, 1969-72 (Folder 1901, Box 140)
  - Palisades Interstate Parks Commission (Folder 1902, Box 141)
  - Palisades Park Site - Con Ed (Folder 1903, Box 141)
  - Parks (Folder 1904, Box 141)
  - Pattern for Progress (Folder 1905, Box 141)
  - Peak Power (see also: Gas Turbines) (Folder 1906, Box 141)
  - Pollution (Air) (Folder 1907, Box 141)
  - Pollution (Air) Articles and Clippings (Folder 1908, Box 141)
  - Pollution - General (Folder 1909, Box 141)
  - Columbia University School of Law - Water Pollution; 3/12/70 (Folder 1910, Box 141)
  - Population Growth (Folder 1911, Box 142)
  - PASNY: Power Authority of New York State (Folder 1912, Box 142)
  - New York Power Crisis - Proposal by Goldberg& Ottinger 8/14/70 (Folder 1913, Box 142)
  - Power Grids (Power Pooling) (Folder 1914, Box 142)
  - Power Lines - Articles&Clippings (Folder 1915, Box 142)
  - Power Lines - Clippings (Folder 1916, Box 142)
  - Power Lines - Chester Co., Pennsylvania (Folder 1917, Box 142)
  - Power Lines - Correspondences (Folder 1918, Box 142)
  - Power Lines - Statements at Hearings; May 4-6, 1966 (Folder 1919, Box 142)
  - Power Lines - Hearings in Washington; May 4-6, 1966 (Folder 1920, Box 143)
  - Power Lines - Legislation (Folder 1921, Box 143)
  - Power Lines - New Jersey (Folder 1922, Box 143)
  - Power Lines - New Jersey (Folder 1923, Box 143)
  - Power Lines - Press Releases (Folder 1924, Box 143)
  - Power Lines - Printed Matter (Folder 1925, Box 143)
  - Power Lines - Statements (Folder 1926, Box 143)
  - Power Plants - Air Storage (Folder 1927, Box 144)
  - Power Plants - Atomic (Folder 1928, Box 144)
  - Power Plants - North Carolina (Folder 1929, Box 144)
  - Power Plants - Taum Sauk (Folder 1930, Box 144)
  - Power Plants - 1970 (Folder 1931, Box 144)
  - Press Contacts (Folder 1932, Box 144)
  - Public Land (Folder 1933, Box 144)
  - Public Service Electric and Gas Co. (New Jersey) (Folder 1934, Box 144)
  - Public Service Law, April 1970 (Folder 1935, Box 144)
  - Public Utility Survey, Investment Dealers Digest; June 6, 1966 (Folder 1936, Box 144)
  - Pumped Storage - Asia (Folder 1937, Box 144)
  - Pumped Storage - Castaic, CA (Folder 1938, Box 144)
  - Pumped Storage - Colorado (Folder 1939, Box 144)
  - Pumped Storage - Europe (Folder 1940, Box 144)
  - Pumped Storage - L. Frankel - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1941, Box 144)
  - Pumped Storage - General (Folder 1942, Box 144)
  - Pumped Storage - General (Folder 1943, Box 145)
  - Pumped Storage - Leakage, Sargent Paper; 6/2/72 (Folder 1944, Box 145)
  - Pumped Storage - Ludington, MI (Folder 1945, Box 145)
  - Pumped Storage - Milwaukee Conference; Sept. 1971 (Folder 1946, Box 145)
  - Pumped Storage - New England (Folder 1947, Box 145)
  - Pumped Storage - Pumped Storage - Printed Matter (Folder 1948, Box 145)
  - Pumped Storage - Southern States (Folder 1949, Box 145)
  - Pumped Storage - Seepage Problems in Reservoirs (Folder 1950, Box 145)
  - Pumped Storage - Proposed Storm King Plant (Folder 1951, Box 145)
  - Pumped Storage - Tabulation (Folder 1952, Box 145)
  - Pumped Storage - Taum Sauk, MO (Folder 1953, Box 146)
  - Pumped Storage - Yard’s Creek, NJ (Folder 1954, Box 146)
  - Quarry - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1955, Box 146)
  - Quotations (Folder 1956, Box 146)
  - Race for Open Space; Extracted for J. Cope - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1957, Box 146)
  - Ads, TV Reports, Magazine and Newspaper Clips, Statistics (Folder 1958, Box 146)
  - Radio&TV: Con Ed - WNEW Radio (Folder 1959, Box 146)
  - Radio&TV: Editorials and Replies (Folder 1960, Box 146)
  - Radio&TV: Letters (Folder 1961, Box 146)
  - Radio&TV: Misc. (Folder 1962, Box 146)
  - Radio&TV: Reports Inc. 1964-65 (Folder 1963, Box 146)
  - Radio&TV: Reports Inc. 1966 (Folder 1964, Box 146)
  - Radio&TV: Reports Inc. 1967-68 (Folder 1965, Box 146)
  - Radio&TV: Reports Inc. Feb.- May 1969 (Folder 1966, Box 147)
  - Radio&TV: Reports Inc. June - Oct. 1969 (Folder 1967, Box 147)
  - Radio&TV: Reports Inc. 1971-72,1974 (Folder 1968, Box 147)
  - Radio 1969 (Folder 1969, Box 147)
  - Radio&TV: Reports 1970 (Folder 1970, Box 147)
  - Railroads (Folder 1971, Box 148)
  - Reclamation - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1972, Box 148)
  - Regional Plan Assoc., 1965 (Folder 1973, Box 148)
  - Registration in Illinois; 9/28/71 (Folder 1974, Box 148)
  - Republican Platform Committee (Folder 1975, Box 148)
  - Reports to Client - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1976, Box 148)
  - Reservoir Capacity; 1964 (Folder 1977, Box 148)
  - Resolutions - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1978, Box 148)
  - Roseton Fossil Fuel Plant (Folder 1979, Box 148)
  - Sandy Hook Marine Lab. (corres.) (Folder 1980, Box 148)
  - Save America’s Natural Beauty - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1981, Box 148)
  - SHPC - Seminars (Folder 1982, Box 148)
  - Scientists’ Committee for Public Information, Inc. (Folder 1983, Box 148)
  - Sportsman’s Council - Hudson Valley (Folder 1984, Box 148)
  - Sportsman’s Show (Folder 1985, Box 148)
  - Statement of Purpose SHPC 1966 (Folder 1986, Box 148)
  - Staten Island (Arthur Kill Atomic Energy Plant) (Folder 1987, Box 148)
  - Staten Island Greenbelt (Folder 1988, Box 148)
  - Stone&Webster (Report on Power Grids) (Folder 1989, Box 148)
  - Clip Sheets - Storm King; 1964 (Folder 1990, Box 148)
  - Mailing, Misc. - L. Frankel: Hudson Valley Project, 1964-65 (Folder 1991, Box 148)
  - Storm King - Kitzmiller File; 1965 (Folder 1992, Box 149)
  - Storm King Case; 1/7/65 (Folder 1993, Box 149)
  - Storm King Issues - Aug. 1966 (Folder 1994, Box 149)
  - Storm King Releases&Background Information (Vandivert File), 1965-66 (Folder 1995, Box 149)
  - Storm King Case, 1966-72 (Folder 1996, Box 149)
  - Taconic State Park Commission - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1997, Box 150)
  - Telegrams, 1966 (Folder 1998, Box 150)
  - Dr. Edward Teller - 1967 Testimony (Folder 1999, Box 150)
  - Testimony Notes - 1964 (Folder 2000, Box 150)
  - Timetable&Status Requests JC (Folder 2001, Box 150)
  - Tourism, 1963-64 (Folder 2002, Box 150)
  - Transmission Lines (Folder 2003, Box 150)
  - United Church vs. FCC (Folder 2004, Box 150)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit - Scenic Hudson Inc., et al Vs. FPC and Con Ed; 1965 (Folder 2005, Box 150)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit - Scenic Hudson, et al Vs. FPC and Con Edison; 1965 - Correspondence (Folder 2006, Box 150)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit - Scenic Hudson, et al - Brief (Folder 2007, Box 150)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit - Scenic Hudson Petition for Review (Folder 2008, Box 150)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals - Scenic Hudson, Inc. - Petition for Review; Dec. 10, 1970 (Folder 2009, Box 150)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit, Scenic Hudson, et al - Petition for Rehearing; Nov. 5, 1971 (Folder 2010, Box 150)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals - Brief for Petitioner, Palisades Interstate Park Commission; Feb. 26, 1971 (Folder 2011, Box 150)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit - Brief for the City of New York; March 1, 1971 (Folder 2012, Box 150)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit - FPC Brief; April 12, 1971 (Folder 2013, Box 150)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit - Con Edison Brief; April 12, 1971 (Folder 2014, Box 150)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit, Scenic Hudson Reply Brief; May 4, 1971 (Folder 2015, Box 151)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit, Notes on the Case: Hearing, June 9, 1971 (Folder 2016, Box 151)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit, Decision; Oct. 22, 1971 (Folder 2017, Box 151)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit, Decision; Oct. 22, 1971 and Judge Oakes dissent (Folder 2018, Box 151)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit - Clippings, News Reports, and Articles; Oct. - Nov. 1971 (Folder 2019, Box 151)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit, Scenic Hudson Petition for Rehearing In Banc; 1971 (Folder 2020, Box 151)
  - Section 27: Federal Power Law, Amendment, January 1972 (Folder 2021, Box 151)
  - New York State Court of Appeals - Scenic Hudson, et al - Brief for Petitioners - Appellants; Nov. 27, 1972 (Folder 2022, Box 151)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit - Greene Co. Planning Board vs. FPC; 1972 (Folder 2023, Box 151)
  - New York State Court of Appeals - Scenic Hudson Press Release, Jan. 11, 1973 (Folder 2024, Box 151)
  - New York State Court of Appeals - Statement by Albert K. Butzel; 3/14/73 (Folder 2025, Box 151)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association, et al, Reply Brief; Jan. 25, 1974 (Folder 2026, Box 151)
  - U.S. Military Academy - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 2027, Box 151)
  - U.S. Press Association re Scenic Hudson (Folder 2028, Box 151)
  - U.S. Supreme Court - Scenic Hudson, et al - Writ of Certiorari to U.S. Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit; 1972 (Folder 2029, Box 151)
  - U.S. Supreme Court - Miscellaneous (Folder 2030, Box 151)
  - Utilities - Advertising (Folder 2031, Box 152)
  - Utilities - Clippings, 1964-68 (Folder 2032, Box 152)
  - Utilities - Clippings, 1969-71 (Folder 2033, Box 152)
  - Utilities - Correspondence and Specific Hearings (Folder 2034, Box 152)
  - Utilities (Other than Con Ed) General Literature (Folder 2035, Box 152)
  - Van Arsdale - Herald Tribune Article - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 2036, Box 152)
  - Wallkill (Folder 2037, Box 152)
  - Walton, Izaak League of America - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 2038, Box 153)
  - Washington Notes (Baker’s) Hudson Valley Project (Folder 2039, Box 153)
  - Waste Disposal and Garbage Burning (Folder 2040, Box 153)
  - Water - Drought; 1965 (Folder 2041, Box 153)
  - Water - Hudson Valley, I (Folder 2042, Box 153)
  - Water - Hudson Valley, II (Folder 2043, Box 153)
  - Water Pollution; 1965-66 (Folder 2044, Box 153)
  - Water Pollution (General) 1968-70, SHPC (Folder 2045, Box 153)
  - Pollution (Water&Air) 1970 (Folder 2046, Box 153)
  - Water Pollution Paper “Grade Teacher Magazine” Winter 1970 (Folder 2047, Box 153)
  - Water Pollution - Bills (Folder 2048, Box 154)
  - Water Pollution - Clippings (Folder 2049, Box 154)
  - Water Pollution - General (Folder 2050, Box 154)
  - Water Pollution - Hudson River (Folder 2051, Box 154)
  - Water Pollution - Hudson Valley (Folder 2052, Box 154)
  - Water Quality - Clippings; 1970-72 (Folder 2053, Box 154)
  - Water Quality Hearings; 1971 (Folder 2054, Box 154)
  - Water Resources Act (Folder 2055, Box 154)
  - Water Resources Commission - Hudson Valley Project, I (Folder 2056, Box 155)
  - Water Resources Commission - Hudson Valley Project, II (Folder 2057, Box 155)
  - Water Resources Commission - Hudson Valley Project, III (Folder 2058, Box 155)
  - Water Resources Commission - Briefs, c. 1964 (Folder 2059, Box 155)
  - Water Shortage; 1965, 1973 (Folder 2060, Box 155)
  - Wetlands Bill (Folder 2061, Box 156)
  - Wilderness Act (Folder 2061a, Box 156)
  - Wilderness Society (Folder 2062, Box 156)
  - Wildlife (Folder 2063, Box 156)
  - Yale Symposium, 1968 (Folder 2064, Box 156)
  - Yorktown (Folder 2065, Box 156)
  - Yorktown (Folder 2066, Box 156)
  - Yorktown (Folder 2067, Box 156)
- 16. Publicity Materials, 1964-1978; 16; About 3 linear feet Boxes: 157 - 165 Folders: 2068 - 2412
  Series contains copies of press releases, membership bulletins, reprints of periodical and newspaper articles, information kits, and background materials. Materials are arranged chronologically. Some of the binders contain related correspondence.
  - Letter Plea re: Black Rock (Folder 2068, Box 157)
  - Release; 9/30/64 (Folder 2069, Box 157)
  - CIC Mailing #1 - Dam Failure; 10/2/64 (Folder 2070, Box 157)
  - Memo to Editorial Writers: Pomeroy Requests Delay; 10/16/64 (Folder 2071, Box 157)
  - Release: Ned Smith (Save America’s Natural Beauty); 11/564 (Folder 2072, Box 157)
  - Re: Bear Mountain Hearings; 11/20/64 (Folder 2073, Box 157)
  - Background FPC; 11/64 (Folder 2074, Box 157)
  - Memo for Editorial Page Editors - Squashes Gov. Rockefeller; 12/12/64 (Folder 2075, Box 157)
  - Memo to Editorial Page Editors; 12/18/64 (Folder 2076, Box 157)
  - “The Hudson River For Whose Utility?” 1964 (Folder 2077, Box 157)
  - Releases and Statements Other than Scenic Hudson (Folder 2078, Box 157)
  - More Supporters Join Fight Against Storm King Plant; 1/6/65 (Folder 2079, Box 157)
  - Release - 1/7/65 (Folder 2080, Box 157)
  - Release - 1/8/65 (Folder 2081, Box 157)
  - Release - Town of Hempstead Joins L.I. Opposition to Storm King; 1/12/65 (Folder 2082, Box 157)
  - Progress Report - 1/14/65 (Folder 2083, Box 157)
  - Memo: L.O. Rothschild re: Swidler; 1/21/65 (Folder 2084, Box 157)
  - Nassau County Fish&Game Association Release; 2/11/65 (Folder 2085, Box 157)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Natural Resources Release; 2/18/65 (Folder 2086, Box 157)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Natural Resources Release; 2/24/65 (Folder 2087, Box 157)
  - Hempstead Town Lands Resources Council Release; 2/24/65 (Folder 2088, Box 157)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Natural Resources Release; 3/2/65 (Folder 2089, Box 157)
  - Release; 3/2/65 (Folder 2090, Box 157)
  - Release; 3/9/65 (Folder 2091, Box 157)
  - SHPC - Dig They Won’t; 3/17/65 (Folder 2092, Box 157)
  - Statement by L.O. Rothschild; 3/22/65 (Folder 2093, Box 157)
  - Release - Cornwall Taxpayers Water Protection Association; 4/5/65 (Folder 2094, Box 157)
  - Release; 4/8/65 (Folder 2095, Box 157)
  - Release - “State Alone is Not Enough” 4/15/65 (Folder 2096, Box 157)
  - Memo to Editors - L.O. Rothschild; 4/23/65 (Folder 2097, Box 157)
  - Rothschild - Release; 4/28/65 (Folder 2098, Box 157)
  - Release; 4/28/65 (Folder 2099, Box 157)
  - Release; May 7, 1965 (Folder 2100, Box 157)
  - Hempstead Town Lands Resources Council Release; 5/13/65 (Folder 2101, Box 157)
  - Memo: Giving Possible Consequences of Non-Action; 6/65 (Folder 2102, Box 157)
  - Special News: “The Time is Now - The Possibilities Infinite” 7/2/65 (Folder 2103, Box 157)
  - Memo to Editors: Petition Filed Asks Review of FPC’s Decision to Grant License; 7/8/65 (Folder 2104, Box 157)
  - Release: “Congressman Dow Helps Scenic Hudson’s Fight…” 7/16/65 (Folder 2105, Box 157)
  - Release; 7/18/65 (Folder 2106, Box 157)
  - Release; 7/19/65 (Folder 2107, Box 157)
  - Memo to Editors: Coming Appearance of Mr. Alexander Lurkis Before the C.C.A.P. Hearings; 7/27/65 (Folder 2108, Box 157)
  - Rod Vandivert Speech; 7/29/65 (Folder 2109, Box 157)
  - Alden: Release - New Yorktown Law Limits Areas for High Power Lines; 8/19/65 (Folder 2110, Box 157)
  - Release - Citizens Committee for the Hudson Valley; 9/13/65 (Folder 2111, Box 157)
  - Statement by Rod Vandivert; 9/29/65 (Folder 2112, Box 157)
  - Background Quarterly to Members; 10/4/65 (Folder 2113, Box 157)
  - Release; 10/15/65 (Folder 2114, Box 157)
  - Release; 11/11/65 (Folder 2115, Box 157)
  - Lurkis: Memo to Editors “NYC’s Blackout Was Predicted” 11/17/65 (Folder 2116, Box 157)
  - Blackout, Background; 12/8/65 (Folder 2117, Box 157)
  - Release; 12/11/65 (Folder 2118, Box 157)
  - Happy Holiday; 12/29/65 (Folder 2119, Box 157)
  - “Storm King&The Power Blackout” by Alexander Saunders; 12/65 (Folder 2120, Box 157)
  - Literature: “The Time is Now&It’s Your Move” 1965 (Folder 2121, Box 157)
  - Special Memo; 1/18/66 (Folder 2122, Box 157)
  - Memo to President&Mr. Saunders Letter; 1/25/66 (Folder 2123, Box 157)
  - Nassau County Fish&Game Association Release; 2/4/66 (Folder 2124, Box 157)
  - Release; 2/14/66 (Folder 2125, Box 157)
  - Scenic Hudson Award Release: Rod&Gun Editors Ass. 2/25/66 (Folder 2126, Box 157)
  - Release; 3/7/66 (Folder 2127, Box 157)
  - The Issue of Storm King Mountain; 3/11/66 (Folder 2128, Box 157)
  - “You Are Urged to Write to the Following…” 3/15/66 (Folder 2129, Box 157)
  - List of Interventions; 3/15/66 (Folder 2130, Box 157)
  - Release; 3/25/66 (Folder 2131, Box 157)
  - Background Memo; 3/1966 (Folder 2132, Box 157)
  - Release; 4/8/66 (Folder 2133, Box 157)
  - Release; 4/23/66 (Folder 2134, Box 157)
  - Release; 4/28/66 (Folder 2135, Box 157)
  - Washington Memorandum: Senate Hearings on Burial of Transition Lines; 5/10/66 (Folder 2136, Box 157)
  - Rod Vandivert Statement; May 31, 1966 (Folder 2137, Box 157)
  - Release - Memo to Editors re: Gas Turbines; June 1966 (Folder 2138, Box 157)
  - Progress Memo to SHPC Activists; 6/8/66 (Folder 2139, Box 157)
  - Release; 6/22/66 (Folder 2140, Box 157)
  - Memo to Editors Page Writers: Resolution Adopted by Hudson River Conservation Society; 6/24/66 (Folder 2141, Box 157)
  - Important Notice Concerning the Natural Area Council; 7/1/66 (Folder 2142, Box 157)
  - Release Concerning St. Louis&Nebraska Power Failures; 7/12/66 (Folder 2143, Box 157)
  - Memo to Citizens Organizing Committee Concerning Eble Letter; 7/13/66 (Folder 2144, Box 157)
  - Release from Fred L. Roth, NYS Historical Ass. 7/15/66 (Folder 2145, Box 157)
  - Suburban Beauty Treatment Seen: Power Lines to Go Underground 8/6/66 (Folder 2146, Box 157)
  - Letter to NY Granges; 8/8/66 (Folder 2147, Box 157)
  - Release from Alexander Lurkis; 8/30/66 (Folder 2148, Box 157)
  - Memo from Cope (to Atkinson, Brower, Carmer, Garrison, Saunders, Sive&Seymour) 9/8/66 (Folder 2149, Box 157)
  - Release - Support of H.R.V. Interstate Compact; 9/8/66 (Folder 2150, Box 157)
  - Release “Why City Hall Let Con Ed Get Away With This One” 9/15/66 (Folder 2151, Box 157)
  - Issue at Storm King Mt. 9/22/66 (Folder 2152, Box 157)
  - Release “Storm King Plan to Tap Aqueduct Said to be Unlawful” 9/22/66 (Folder 2153, Box 157)
  - Statement by L.O. Rothschild (Jet Turbine Generators) 10/3/66 (Folder 2154, Box 157)
  - Letter from Mrs. Whitney N. Seymour to Citizens Organizing Committee; 10/5/66 (Folder 2155, Box 157)
  - NYS Conservation Council Inc. - Release; 10/6/66 (Folder 2156, Box 157)
  - Literature: Capsule Report; Oct. 11, 1966 (Folder 2157, Box 157)
  - Memo for the Information of Editors; 10/17/66 (Folder 2158, Box 157)
  - Release “Dozen Eminent Men” 10/18/66 (Folder 2159, Box 157)